{
    "id": "08bb833499304dc0ae27823129219e83",
    "title": "Grammar exercise: used to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2870743c8e874dbe8cd8a3e0b6e71cc7",
            "title": "Used To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I am quite used to ………………….. hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She used to …………………… a lot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "write",
                        "writing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am not used to ………………… on the right.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drive",
                        "driving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………., but now I have stopped.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was used to smoking",
                        "used to smoke",
                        "used to smoking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… western music, but now I do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't use to like",
                        "didn't use to liking",
                        "was not used to liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I found it difficult to get ………………… in such a cold climate.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to live",
                        "used to living"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… very hard last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "worked",
                        "used to work"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. be afraid of spiders.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "was used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… .. a big car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wasn't used to driving",
                        "wasn't used to drive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ............................................. hard when I was at university.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to work",
                        "used to working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}